<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-10-20T09:59:52+00:00</updated><id>https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Joshua Conversational AI Ecosystem</title><subtitle>We present Joshua, a conversational AI ecosystem designed to achieve unbounded capability through natural language interaction. Unlike traditional systems where capabilities are pre-programmed, Joshua acquires new abilities on demand through conversation, building its own tools via meta-programming and continuously improving through self-reflection. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Announcing the RMDev Research Project Website</title><link href="https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/blog/2025/project-launch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing the RMDev Research Project Website"/><published>2025-10-18T18:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-10-18T18:30:00+00:00</updated><id>https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/blog/2025/project-launch</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rmdevpro.github.io/rmdev-pro/blog/2025/project-launch/"><![CDATA[<p>We’re excited to announce the launch of the official RMDev Research Project website!</p> <h2 id="what-this-site-offers">What This Site Offers</h2> <p>This website serves as the central hub for our groundbreaking research on LLM development methodologies. Here you’ll find:</p> <h3 id="research-papers">Research Papers</h3> <p>Access our comprehensive research papers exploring systematic approaches to large language model development. Our first paper analyzes over 10,000 conversational fragments to identify best practices and emergent patterns.</p> <p><a href="/papers/">Browse Research Papers →</a></p> <h3 id="conversational-fragments">Conversational Fragments</h3> <p>One of our key innovations is the systematic preservation of development conversations. We’ve made thousands of these fragments searchable, providing unprecedented transparency into the development process.</p> <p><a href="/search/">Search Fragments →</a></p> <h3 id="downloadable-artifacts">Downloadable Artifacts</h3> <p>Throughout our research, we’ve developed tools and applications that implement our findings. All artifacts are freely available for download and use.</p> <p><a href="/artifacts/">View Artifacts →</a></p> <h3 id="community-discussion">Community Discussion</h3> <p>We believe in open collaboration and welcome community input. Join discussions about our research, ask questions, or share your own experiences with LLM-driven development.</p> <p><a href="https://github.com/YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/rmdev-pro/discussions">Join Discussions →</a></p> <h2 id="why-this-matters">Why This Matters</h2> <p>Large language models are transforming software development, but systematic understanding of best practices remains limited. Our research addresses this gap through:</p> <ol> <li><strong>Systematic Data Collection</strong>: Preserving complete development histories</li> <li><strong>Rigorous Analysis</strong>: Identifying patterns across thousands of interactions</li> <li><strong>Practical Validation</strong>: Testing findings in real-world projects</li> <li><strong>Open Sharing</strong>: Making data and findings freely available</li> </ol> <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2> <p>In the coming weeks and months, we’ll be:</p> <ul> <li>Publishing additional research papers</li> <li>Releasing more conversational fragments</li> <li>Developing and sharing new tools</li> <li>Engaging with the community</li> </ul> <p>Stay tuned for regular updates on this blog!</p> <h2 id="get-involved">Get Involved</h2> <p>Whether you’re a researcher, developer, or simply interested in LLM development, we invite you to:</p> <ul> <li>Read our research papers</li> <li>Explore the conversational fragments</li> <li>Try our tools</li> <li>Join the discussion</li> <li>Provide feedback</li> </ul> <p>We’re committed to advancing the field of LLM-driven software development through open research and collaboration.</p> <hr/> <p><em>Have questions or want to contribute? Visit our <a href="https://github.com/YOUR_GITHUB_USERNAME/rmdev-pro/discussions">GitHub Discussions</a> or contact us at contact@rmdev.pro</em></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="announcement"/><category term="news"/><category term="website"/><category term="project-update"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the launch of the official RMDev Research Project website!]]></summary></entry></feed>